{
    "id": "85099d4f10b0438f9635da505105ac54",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How much will it cost to overhaul the motor? Overhaul can be replaced by …………………..",
            "description": "Revamp means the same as overhaul.",
            "answers": [
                "regig",
                "revamp",
                "rip"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you mean to leave the door unlocked or was it an oversight? Oversight can be replaced by ………………………………?",
            "description": "Oversight means the same ad heedlessness. ",
            "answers": [
                "scrupulousness",
                "diligence",
                "heedlessness"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The waiter was furious at being given such a paltry tip. Paltry can be replaced by ………………………..",
            "description": "Paltry means measly. ",
            "answers": [
                "measly",
                "resolute",
                "resourceful"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She pampers her husband like a baby. Pampers can be replaced by ……………………….",
            "description": "Pampers means the same as indulges.",
            "answers": [
                "indulges",
                "pacifies",
                "patronizes"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Pandemonium broke out when the teacher left the room. Pandemonium can be replaced by ………………………….",
            "description": "Both words mean chaos.",
            "answers": [
                "bedlam",
                "mischief",
                "malevolence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The child led a cloistered life. Here cloistered can be replaced by ………………………..",
            "description": "Cloistered and insulated can both mean the same.",
            "answers": [
                "insinuated",
                "insulated",
                "reserved"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Certain drugs cause blood to coagulate. Here coagulate can be replaced by ………………………………..",
            "description": "Both words mean clot.",
            "answers": [
                "curdle",
                "ambulate",
                "percolate"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The retiring chairman received a panegyric from the new chairman. Here panegyric can be replaced by ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tribute",
                "encomium",
                "eulogy",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The bedrooms were painted in pastel colors. Pastel can be replaced by …………………………",
            "description": "Pastels can mean light or muted.",
            "answers": [
                "light",
                "vibrant",
                "dark"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When you ask him a question you get a pedantic answer. Here pedantic can be replaced by ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "succinct",
                "pithy",
                "didactic"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He had a penchant for rich desserts. Here penchant can be replaced by ……………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "aversion",
                "repulsion",
                "propensity"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}